Randy Larson

Senior UI/UX Designer and Product Owner

Salt Lake City, UT 84105 randy.larson@gmail.com 801-898-7335

SUMMARY

Senior UI/UX Designer with over 20 years in Website and Web Application development. Product Owner with extensive experience in front-end development, planning, wireframe, prototyping, user interface/interaction design, and team management. Experience with responsive concepts, mobile design, usability and accessibility.

EXPERIENCE

Division 6, Raleigh, NC — *Lead UI/UX Designer & Developer and Product Owner*

MARCH 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2022

Responsible for Website, Web App and Mobile App planning, design and front-end development. Product Lead in charge of design standards and development team on the World's first and only Social Influence Stock Market, influence.inc.

- Wireframe, Prototype and HTML/CSS heavy workflow on over 15 projects.
- 18-month development cycle to conceptualize, design and launch start-up with a budget of \$500,000.
- Managed and worked directly with React Developers, Database Engineers, Integration Specialists and Cloud Engineer to create one-of-a-kind software service.
- Worked within numerous systems, frameworks, and libraries including Wordpress, React, Angular, Strapi, and custom CMS systems.

Big Bang Media, Los Angeles, CA — Senior UI/UX Designer and Developer

JULY 2001 - AUGUST 2022

Lead Front-end Designer and Developer for Toyota USA, Lexus USA and Waste Management.

PORTFOLIO

timebombproductions.com

SOCIAL LINKS

instagram.com/ftfbass linkedin.com/in/randytheronlarson

SKILLS

HTML / CSS / SASS

Bootstrap Framework

Adobe Creative Suite

XD / Figma / Sketch

Web Design

User Interface (UI)

User Experience (UX)

Graphic Design

Problem Solving

Communication Skills

Time Management

Project Management

Responsible for planning, prototyping, designing and coding numerous nationwide campaigns for primary and secondary markets.

- Complete redesign and restructure of Toyota and Lexus Puerto Rico Sites to meet Toyota styles and guidelines.
- Created and maintained user interface for Toyota "Wheel Stand" point of sale system on 200 devices, at over 20 Auto Shows internationally for 5 years running.
- Creation of national dealership rental car system which increased online reservations by 35%.
- Responsible for creation and maintenance of a national contest system for WM, used in 17 US and Canadian markets which awards over \$25,000 quarterly to its users.
- Maintained French and Spanish versions of sites requiring concepts and layouts specific to localization.

Timebomb Productions, Salt Lake City, UT — *Designer, Developer, Consultant*

MAY 1997 - PRESENT

Web and graphic design services for individuals, companies and agencies. Web design, planning, strategy and creation, promotional materials, printing, apparel, advertising, photo editing.

- Worked directly with advertising agencies, Riester Robb Harris & Love (Salt Lake City, UT) and the Three Thirty Group (Los Angeles, CA) to create products for over 35 client properties.
- Industries serviced include ski resorts, casinos, car dealerships, movie and video game production, housing developments, startups and more.

EDUCATION

Salt Lake Community College, Salt Lake City, UT

SEPTEMBER 1994 - JUNE 1996

Associate in Arts (AA) in Graphic Design with Computer Design Specialization